let dorsal_trials = [
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_11', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_13', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_16', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_20', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_25', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AAG_AAK_3_30', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '10', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AAG_AAK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_11', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_13', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_16', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_20', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_25', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'AHG_AHK_3_30', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '14', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/AHG_AHK_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_11', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_13', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_16', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_20', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_25', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'IHG_IHK_5_30', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '12', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/IHG_IHK_5_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '4', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '7', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_11', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_13', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '13', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_16', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_16.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_20', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_25', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_25.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>K</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>G</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'syllable', audio: 'UHG_UHK_5_30', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '6', voiced_sel: 'G', voiceless_sel: 'K', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', path: 'audio/syllables/UHG_UHK_5_30.wav' }},]